secure-decoration.com 2018-11-18

# Privacy and Cookie Policy - DecoNetwork

DecoNetwork Pty Ltd is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the DecoNetwork Pty Ltd Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the DecoNetwork Pty Ltd website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

##  Collection of your Personal Information

DecoNetwork Pty Ltd collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. DecoNetwork Pty Ltd also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by DecoNetwork. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by DecoNetwork Pty Ltd for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the DecoNetwork Pty Ltd Web site.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through DecoNetwork Pty Ltd public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: DecoNetwork Pty Ltd does not read any of your private online communications.

DecoNetwork Pty Ltd encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from DecoNetwork Pty Ltd so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. DecoNetwork Pty Ltd is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the DecoNetwork Pty Ltd and DecoNetwork Pty Ltd family of Web sites.

##  Credit Card Information

Any credit card detail collected are attained via a secure site and are fully encrypted and are used by payment gateways only for the purposes of processing payments. Credit card information is not available nor supplied to any third parties for any purpose what so ever.

##  Use of your Personal Information

DecoNetwork Pty Ltd collects and uses your personal information to operate the DecoNetwork Pty Ltd Web site and deliver the services you have requested. DecoNetwork Pty Ltd also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from DecoNetwork Pty Ltd and its affiliates. DecoNetwork Pty Ltd may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

DecoNetwork Pty Ltd does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. DecoNetwork Pty Ltd may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, DecoNetwork Pty Ltd may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to DecoNetwork, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

DecoNetwork Pty Ltd does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

DecoNetwork Pty Ltd keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within DecoNetwork, in order to determine what DecoNetwork Pty Ltd services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within DecoNetwork Pty Ltd to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

##  Use of Cookies

The DecoNetwork Pty Ltd Web site use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

###  1st party Cookies used on this site

The following 1st party cookies are used on our site:

**Name** |  **Purpose**  
---|---  
login_token |  Allows the user to be automatically logged in if they have previously entered their username and password.  
_pc_session_id |  Allows our site to store information about session (referrer, landing page, etc...)  
c_rt_ppr |  Allows DecoNetwork to apply session affinity to back-end nodes in cluster.  
set_sa |  Used on the sign-up page to store what DecoNetwork sales agent website has originally been visited.  
dn_partner |  Logs the DecoNetwork partner referral website which the DecoNetwork.com visitor first visited.  
  
###  3rd party Cookies used on this site

The following 3rd party cookies are used on our site:

**Provider** |  **Name** |  **Purpose** |  **More information**  
---|---|---|---  
Google |  _utma  
_utmb  
_utmc  
_utmz |  These cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use our site. We use the information to compile reports and to help us improve the site. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the site, where visitors have come to the site from and the pages they visited. |  [Google Privacy policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/)  
  
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize DecoNetwork Pty Ltd pages, or register with DecoNetwork Pty Ltd site or services, a cookie helps DecoNetwork Pty Ltd to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same DecoNetwork Pty Ltd Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the DecoNetwork Pty Ltd features that you customized.

###  How to control and delete cookies

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the DecoNetwork Pty Ltd services or Web sites you visit.

Visit [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) which contains comprehensive information on how to do this on a wide variety of browsers. You will also find details on how to delete cookies from your machine as well as more general information about cookies.

To opt-out of third-parties collecting any data regarding your interaction on our website, please refer to their websites for further information.

##  Security of your Personal Information

DecoNetwork Pty Ltd secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. DecoNetwork Pty Ltd secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

##  Changes to this Statement

DecoNetwork Pty Ltd will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. DecoNetwork Pty Ltd encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how DecoNetwork Pty Ltd is protecting your information.

##  Contact Information

DecoNetwork Pty Ltd welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that DecoNetwork Pty Ltd has not adhered to this Statement, please contact DecoNetwork Pty Ltd at [info@deconetwork.com](mailto:info@deconetwork.com) We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
